Finding Aid for Donald S. Leonard Papers 1925-1966
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Organization and Activities Files
  - Permanent Legislative Committee 1944-1963
    - Minutes and reports
      - 1944-1951 (Box 31)
      - 1953 (Box 31)
      - 1954-1955 (Box 31)
      - 1956-1957 (Box 31)
      - 1958-1959 (Box 31)
      - 1960-1961 (Box 31)
      - 1962-1963 (Box 31)
    - Subcommittee on State Constitutional Convention 1961-1962
      - Minutes and correspondence, 3 folders (Box 31)
      - Search and seizure provisions, 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Liquor Control Commission 1961-1966
    - General descriptions, facts and figures (Box 31)
    - Rules and regulations, policy statements (Box 31)
    - Policy notebook (Box 31)
    - Licensing procedures and forms (Box 31)
    - State Government Reorganization (Box 31)
    - Data Processing Section Review Program (Box 31)
    - Commission meeting notes February 1966-April 1966 (Box 31)
    - Roseville Investigation
      - Correspondence and transcripts (Box 31)
      - Summary report (Box 31)
    - Reports and statistics (Box 31)
    - Liquor legislation 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Correspondence and notes 1961-1966, 2 folders (Box 31)
    - Meeting with Package Liquor Dealers Association 1965 (Box 31)
    - Liquor Control Study Trip to Scandinavia
      - Finland (Box 31)
      - Norway and Sweden (Box 31)
      - Final reports (Box 31)
    - National Alcoholic Beverage Control Association
      - Constitution and pamphlets (Box 31)
      - NABCA Review 1964-1966 (Box 31)
      - Meeting 1965 (Box 31)
    - Liquor control in other states (Box 31)
    - Clippings undated, 1963-1966, 4 folders (Box 31)
  - Citizens Advisory Committee on Equal Educational Opportunities 1961-1962
    - Minutes (Box 32)
    - Statements and reports, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Draft final report, 5 folders (Box 32)
    - Final report (Box 32)
    - School board action and commentaries (Box 32)
    - Clippings (Box 32)
  - Bar Associations
    - American Bar Association 1953 (Box 32)
    - Michigan Bar Association
      - Committee on Criminal Jurisprudence 1960-1966, 2 folders (Box 32)
      - Wiretapping 1956-1962 (Box 32)
      - Minor Court Reorganization 1965-1966, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Detroit Bar Association-Civil Rights Committee 1957-1963 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous Activities
    - Boy Scouts 1953-1954 (Box 32)
    - Citizens' Advisory Committee on Police Procedures, Detroit 1960 (Box 32)
    - Detroit Junior Board of Commerce 1952-1953 (Box 32)
    - Hundred Club 1953 (Box 32)
    - March of Dimes 1953-1954 (Box 32)
    - Metropolitan Police Academy of Michigan 1961-1966, 2 folders (Box 32)
    - Office of Price Administration 1943 (Box 32)
    - Order of Founders and Patriots 1949-1959 (Box 32)
    - Republican State Central Committee 1965 (Box 32)
    - Sons of the American Revolution 1952-1954 (Box 32)
    - Southeastern Michigan Association of Chiefs of Police 1944-1963 (Box 32)
    - United Foundation 1953-1954 (Box 32)
    - U.S. Naval Reserve, commission in 1940 (Box 32)
    - U.S. Park Police, Survey of 1956 (Box 32)
    - Wayne County Recorders Court 1966 (Box 32)
    - Wayne University 1948-1959 (Box 32)
- Audio-Visual Materials
  Audio-Visual Materials, except for one sound recording, consists of photographs from different periods in Leonard's career.
  - Photographs
    - Personal
      - Informal (Box 33)
      - Portraits (Box 33)
      - Portraits of others (Box 33)
    - Civil Defense 1941-1952
      - Aircraft Warning Service 1943 (Box 33)
      - Paraguayan president's visit 1943 (Box 33)
      - Sault Ste. Marie mock nuclear attack exercise 1951 (Box 33)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 33)
    - Michigan State Police 1929-1952
      - Donald S. Leonard alone (Box 33)
      - DSL with others (Box 33)
      - Airplane crash, Lansing 1949 (Box 33)
      - Buildings (Box 33)
      - Exhibits (Box 33)
      - File room (Box 33)
      - Fingerprinting (Box 33)
      - House Un-American Activities Committee hearing 1952 (Box 33)
      - Jackson Prison riot 1952 (Box 33)
        (includes photos of Leonard and G. Mennen Williams)
      - Laboratory work (Box 33)
      - Personnel (Box 33)
      - Polygraph (Box 33)
      - Queen Juliana visit 1952 (Box 33)
      - Radio equipment (Box 33)
      - Recruit school (Box 33)
      - Recruits with DSL (Box 33)
      - Reuther shooting suspects 1948-1949 (Box 33)
      - Sigler with DS: (Box 33)
      - Sojourner Truth Housing Project, Detroit 1942 (Box 33)
      - State Office Building fire, Lansing 1951 (Box 33)
      - Strikes at Ford, Shakespeare, and other sites (Box 33)
      - Suspects (Box 33)
      - Training (Box 33)
      - Vehicles-Airplanes, automobiles, horses, motorcycles (Box 33)
      - Veterans refresher course (Box 33)
      - Williams inauguration 1951 (Box 33)
    - Detroit Police Department 1952-1955
      (see also outsize photos in UAm folder)
      - Personnel (Box 33)
        (most also include DSL)
      - Tornadoes at Flint and Port Huron 1953
        - Prints (Box 33)
        - Negatives (Box 33)
    - Politics 1952-1954
      - 1952 campaign (Box 33)
      - 1954 campaign
        - Convention (Box 33)
        - State Fair? (Box 33)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 33)
    - Organizations
      - International Association of Chief of Police (Box 33)
      - Liquor Control Commission (Box 33)
      - Michigan Association of Chiefs of Police (Box 33)
  - Sound Recording
    [Digitized audio files are only available in the Bentley Historical Library reading room on designated Bentley Library computers.]
    - Speech given during campaign for governor, 1952, Audio Reel-to-Reel, 5 inch, 1 7/8 ips
      - [Part 1], [85530-SR-1-1]; mp3 file; (Tape content does not match original description; recording of a crowd of people clapping. Separate recording of the Bob Hope Show with Bing Crosby.)
      - [Part 2], [85530-SR-1-2]; mp3 file; (Discussing the economy, the threat of Communism, and Federal control of state and local governments.)